<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata>
    <idinfo>
        <citation>
            <citeinfo>
                <title>Shoreline Public Access</title>
                <onlink>https://geodata.hawaii.gov/arcgis/rest/services/CoastalMarine/MapServer/25</onlink>
                <onlink>https://files.hawaii.gov/dbedt/op/gis/data/shoreline_public_access_oah.pdf</onlink>
            </citeinfo>
        </citation>
        <descript>
            <abstract>[Metadata]  Description: Location of public shoreline access ways on Oahu as of 2008. June 2024:  Hawaii Statewide GIS Program staff removed extraneous fields 
that had been added as part of a 2016 GIS database conversion and were
 no longer needed.  For additional information, please refer to metadata at https://files.hawaii.gov/dbedt/op/gis/data/shoreline_public_access_oah.pdf or contact Hawaii Statewide GIS Program, Office of Planning, State of Hawaii; PO Box 2359, Honolulu, Hi. 96804; (808) 587-2846; email: gis@hawaii.gov; Website: https://planning.hawaii.gov/gis.Source : NOAA Fisheries, City and County of Honolulu’s Department of Planning &amp;amp; Permitting, and the State of Hawaii Office of Planning.</abstract>
            <purpose>This dataset contains the locations of Oahu public shoreline access ways, as of 2008.</purpose>
        </descript>
        <keywords>
            <theme>
                <themekt>None</themekt>
                <themekey>Shoreline Public Access</themekey>
                <themekey>Hawaii</themekey>
                <themekey>Oahu</themekey>
                <themekey>NOAA</themekey>
                <themekey>HawaiiStateGIS</themekey>
                <themekey>histategis</themekey>
                <themekey>Ocean</themekey>
                <themekey>PROW</themekey>
                <themekey>BROW</themekey>
                <themekey>Beach Access</themekey>
                <themekey>Right of Way</themekey>
            </theme>
        </keywords>
        <accconst>None</accconst>
        <useconst>State of Hawaii Terms of Use. 



The
 contents of this web page are public domain and to the extent indicated
 otherwise in the Terms of Use, are exempt from Terms of Use policy 
restrictions.There are no expressed warranties associated with the 
release of this data or product. Specifically, no warranty is made that 
the GIS data or any subsequent updates will be error free and no 
warranty is made regarding the positional or thematic accuracy of the 
GIS data. The GIS data and any features depicted do not represent or 
confer any legal rights, privileges, benefits, boundaries or claims of 
any kind. The Office of Planning and Sustainable Development encourages users to report any 
discrepancies or errors found. 
 Contact: Hawaii Statewide GIS Program, Office of Planning and 
Sustainable Development, State of Hawaii; PO Box 2359, Honolulu, Hi. 
96804; (808) 587-2846; email: gis@hawaii.gov. Website: https://planning.hawaii.gov/gis.</useconst>
        <datacred>Hawaii Statewide GIS Program, NOAA Fisheries, C&amp;C of Honolulu DPP</datacred>
    </idinfo>
    <metainfo>
        <metd>20191005</metd>
        <metc>
            <cntinfo>
                <!--no contact person or organization name available-->
            </cntinfo>
        </metc>
        <metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
        <metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
        <mettc>local time</mettc>
    </metainfo>
</met